Ting Han Gan - Computer Science Student specialised in Data Science

https://tinghan-gan.com

Hard-working computer science student majoring in Data Science, with 3+ years of proven interpersonal and organisation skills of customer service in high intensity environments.

Seeking to contribute to a challenging workplace as a data analyst that strives in innovation to broaden knowledge and aim to help achieve company goals. Bilingual in English and Mandarin.



tinghan68@gmail.com



0478-839-328



In linkedin.com/in/ting-han-gan/



github.com/TingHanGan

TECHNICAL (IT) SKILLS

Data Management Data Analysis, Pattern & Trend Identification, Visualisation of Data Insights, Creation of clean

reports using R Markdown & PDFs

Computer Science

Proficient with R, Rscript, Python, Juypter Notebook, Tableau, Java, Troubleshooting

Experience in MySQL, Excel, Javascript, HTML/CSS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tsuru Japanese Restaurant, Melbourne VIC — Part Time

JANUARY 2021 - CURRENT

- Gained the trust to supervise and conduct staff training.
- Liaised between both kitchens and staff to ensure quality customer service is met.
- Managed reservations and stock count of drinks daily.

Crystal Palace Catering, Melbourne VIC — *Part Time*

JANUARY 2019 – JANUARY 2021

- Worked as an effective team member and leader to take orders and serve food in a range of diverse teams.
- Learnt the ability to balance workloads efficiently in a constantly changing and high intensity environment.
- Checked in with guests to uphold the company values of excellent customer service.

EDUCATION

Monash University, Clayton VIC

JANUARY 2019 - CURRENT

Bachelor of Computer Science

Major in Data Science; Minors in Business Information Systems and Korean

McKinnon Secondary College, McKinnon VIC – Victorian Certificate of Education

JANUARY 2013 - DECEMBER 2018

Graduated at a VCE Level

UNIVERSITY PROJECT

Covid-19 Data Collection and Tracing Application

JANUARY 2021 - CURRENT

- Led the group project as a Scrum master with management tools, to ensure we are on track.
- Built multiple live interactive Tableau dashboards (e.g., Daily updates) connected to Google Sheets as a server to visualise relevant statistics of Covid-19, saving 3 hours a day of manual updating.
- Analysed data from 15+ sources to perform analysis and present results in Tableau and R Graphs.
- Utilised and created a website to store our data analysis findings and corresponding reports.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Quantium, Virtual Internship Experience Program 2021

AUGUST 2021

Participated in the open access Quantium Virtual Experience Program with Forage

Tasks Completed include:

- Conducted and identified insights on client's dataset to provide commercial recommendations.
- Extended the previous analysis to test the impact of given trial stores using hypothesis testing.
- Prepared a report regarding analytics and commercial application for the client.

Accenture, Virtual Internship Experience Program 2021

AUGUST 2021

Participated in the open access Accenture Virtual Experience Program with Forage

Tasks Completed include:

- Identified crucial priorities for the project plan for client.
- Reviewed multiple sources and interpret, extract, and combine data through performing data analysis.
- Understood and identified Key Performance Indicators (KPI).

IT/CS Peer Mentor, Clayton VIC - Volunteer

JANUARY 2020 – JUNE 2020

- Assisted first years with any questions they had by planning information and social events.
- Ensured the smooth transition from high school to university for mentees.
- Developed necessary planning and leadership skills.